likazing.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy | xuNETWORK

## Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit our websites, and how we safeguard your information. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

## 1\. Introduction

Our company (" _us,_ " " _we,_ " or " _Company_ ") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Websites (" _the Sites_ "). We created this website Privacy Policy (" _Privacy Policy_ ") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Sites, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Sites, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Sites, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Information Collection Practices

### 2.1. Types Of Information Collected

#### (a) Traffic Data Collected

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: (1) IP addresses; (2) domain servers; (3) types of computers accessing the Sites; and (4) types of web browsers used to access the Sites (collectively " _Traffic Data_ "). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Sites. We also may use " _cookies_ " to customize content specific to your interests.

#### (b) Personal Information Collected

In order for you to download products that we offer via the Sites, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you (" _Personal Information_ "). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name and e-mail address) and (2) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and income). If you communicate with us by e-mail or post messages, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

### 2.2. Uses Of Information Collected

#### (a) Company Use Of Information

We use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Sites, displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.

#### (b) Sharing Of Personal Information

We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We share Demographic Data with advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate (i.e., non-personally-identifiable) basis. We do not share Contact Data with other companies who may want to send you information about their products or services. We share Contact Data with our business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Sites. Those business partners have all agreed to uphold the same standards of security and confidentiality that we have promised to you in this Privacy Policy, and they will only use your Contact Data and other Personal Information to carry out their specific business obligations to Company. If you do not want us to share your Contact Data with any third parties, please contact us. Please understand that such a request will likely limit your ability to take advantage of all of the features and services we offer on the Sites.

#### (c) User Choice Regarding Collection, Use, And Distribution Of Personal Information

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Sites; however you will not be able to access and use those portions of the Sites that require your Personal Information. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or from some of our partners, you may select the appropriate " _opt-out_ " option each time we ask you for Personal Information or simply refuse to provide it as appropriate when asked.

## 3\. Confidentiality And Security Of Personal Information

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; or (c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit you Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

### 3.1. Public Information

The Sites contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also may make commenting available to you on certain pages. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

## 4\. Third Party Advertisements/Google Ads

This site also uses third party advertisements to generate revenue. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our website, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security, McAfee and Eset.com. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### 4.1: Google Advertising Cookie And Doubleclick Dart Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users of our site based on their visit to our website and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

## 5\. Updates And Changes To Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Sites and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Sites.

## 6\. Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

## 7\. Contact Information And Policy Updates

### 7.1. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us.

### 7.2. Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Sites and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Sites. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.
